{
  "articles" : [
  {
    "id": 1,
    "name": "Knitted Jumper",
    "detail": "Knitted jumper with a crew neck",
    "category": "Oberteile",
    "brand": "QS by s.Oliver",
    "price": 29.99,
    "tags": { "new": "true", "sustainable": "true", "premium": "false" },
    "wishList": false,
    "shoppingCart": false,
    "colorVariants": [
      {
        "color": {
          "variant": "LightGrey",
          "group": "Grey",
          "value": "#bdbdbd"
        },
        "pictures": {
          "front": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2141220.9730_front",
          "flat": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2141220.9730_flat",
          "back": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2141220.9730_back",
          "outfit": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2141220.9730_outfit"
        }
      },
      {
        "color": {
          "variant": "LightBrown",
          "group": "Brown",
          "value": "#a1887f"
        },
        "pictures": {
          "front": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2141220.83W0_front",
          "flat": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2141220.83W0_flat",
          "back": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2141220.83W0_back",
          "outfit": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2141220.83W0_outfit"
        }
      },
      {
        "color": {
          "variant": "RoyalBlue",
          "group": "Blue",
          "value": "#1a237e"
        },
        "pictures": {
          "front": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2141220.5884_front",
          "flat": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2141220.5884_flat",
          "back": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2141220.5884_back",
          "outfit": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2141220.5884_outfit"
        }
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "name": "T-shirt",
    "detail": "T-shirt with an all-over print",
    "category": "Oberteile",
    "brand": "QS by s.Oliver",
    "price": 19.99,
    "tags": { "new": "true", "sustainable": "false", "premium": "false" },
    "wishList": false,
    "shoppingCart": false,
    "colorVariants": [
      {
        "color": {
          "variant": "LightGreen",
          "group": "Green",
          "value": "#aed581"
        },
        "pictures": {
          "front": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2140283.73A0_front",
          "flat": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2140283.73A0_flat",
          "back": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2140283.73A0_back",
          "outfit": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2140283.73A0_outfit"
        }
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "name": "Cotton T-shirt",
    "detail": "Cotton T-shirt with a slub yarn texture",
    "category": "Oberteile",
    "brand": "QS by s.Oliver",
    "price": 12.99,
    "tags": { "new": "true", "sustainable": "true", "premium": "false" },
    "wishList": false,
    "shoppingCart": false,
    "colorVariants": [
      {
        "color": {
          "variant": "White",
          "group": "White",
          "value": "#ffffff"
        },
        "pictures": {
          "front": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2141633.0100_front",
          "flat": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2141633.0100_flat",
          "back": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2141633.0100_back",
          "outfit": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2141633.0100_outfit"
        }
      },
      {
        "color": {
          "variant": "Black",
          "group": "Black",
          "value": "#000000"
        },
        "pictures": {
          "front": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2141633.9999_front",
          "flat": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2141633.9999_flat",
          "back": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2141633.9999_back",
          "outfit": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2141633.9999_outfit"
        }
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "name": "Dress Shirt",
    "detail": "Slim fit: cotton blend dress shirt",
    "category": "Oberteile",
    "brand": "s.Oliver BLACK LABEL",
    "price": 49.99,
    "tags": { "new": "true", "sustainable": "true", "premium": "true" },
    "wishList": false,
    "shoppingCart": false,
    "colorVariants": [
      {
        "color": {
          "variant": "White",
          "group": "White",
          "value": "#ffffff"
        },
        "pictures": {
          "front": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2145478.0100_front",
          "flat": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2145478.0100_flat",
          "back": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2145478.0100_back",
          "outfit": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2145478.0100_outfit"
        }
      },
      {
        "color": {
          "variant": "RoyalBlue",
          "group": "Blue",
          "value": "#1a237e"
        },
        "pictures": {
          "front": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2145478.5978_front",
          "flat": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2145478.5978_flat",
          "back": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2145478.5978_back",
          "outfit": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2145478.5978_outfit"
        }
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "name": "Cotton Blend Shirt",
    "detail": "Slim fit: Cotton blend shirt",
    "category": "Oberteile",
    "brand": "s.Oliver BLACK LABEL",
    "price": 59.99,
    "tags": { "new": "true", "sustainable": "false", "premium": "true" },
    "wishList": false,
    "shoppingCart": false,
    "colorVariants": [
      {
        "color": {
          "variant": "Bordeaux",
          "group": "Brown",
          "value": "#bcaaa4"
        },
        "pictures": {
          "front": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2142866.39G2_front",
          "flat": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2142866.39G2_flat",
          "back": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2142866.39G2_back",
          "outfit": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2142866.39G2_outfit"
        }
      },
      {
        "color": {
          "variant": "SkyBlue",
          "group": "Blue",
          "value": "#b3e5fc"
        },
        "pictures": {
          "front": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2142866.53G2_front",
          "flat": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2142866.53G2_flat",
          "back": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2142866.53G2_back",
          "outfit": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2142866.53G2_outfit"
        }
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "name": "Long Sleeve Shirt",
    "detail": "Slim fit: long sleeve shirt with a patch breast pocket",
    "category": "Oberteile",
    "brand": "s.Oliver",
    "price": 39.99,
    "tags": { "new": "true", "sustainable": "false", "premium": "false" },
    "wishList": false,
    "shoppingCart": false,
    "colorVariants": [
      {
        "color": {
          "variant": "LightGreen",
          "group": "Green",
          "value": "#689f38"
        },
        "pictures": {
          "front": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2140657.7450_front",
          "flat": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2140657.7450_flat",
          "back": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2140657.7450_back",
          "outfit": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2140657.7450_outfit"
        }
      },
      {
        "color": {
          "variant": "Lightblue",
          "group": "Blue",
          "value": "#b3e5fc"
        },
        "pictures": {
          "front": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2140657.5084_front",
          "flat": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2140657.5084_flat",
          "back": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2140657.5084_back",
          "outfit": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2140657.5084_outfit"
        }
      },
      {
        "color": {
          "variant": "DarkGrey",
          "group": "Grey",
          "value": "#424242"
        },
        "pictures": {
          "front": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2140657.5978_front",
          "flat": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2140657.5978_flat",
          "back": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2140657.5978_back",
          "outfit": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2140657.5978_outfit"
        }
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "name": "Shawn Jeans",
    "detail": "Shawn jeans / regular fit / mid rise / slim leg",
    "category": "Unterteile",
    "brand": "QS by s.Oliver",
    "price": 59.99,
    "tags": { "new": "true", "sustainable": "false", "premium": "false" },
    "wishList": false,
    "shoppingCart": false,
    "colorVariants": [
      {
        "color": {
          "variant": "Blue",
          "group": "Blue",
          "value": "#0d47a1"
        },
        "pictures": {
          "front": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2141260.55Z6_front",
          "flat": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2141260.55Z6_flat",
          "back": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2141260.55Z6_back",
          "outfit": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2141260.55Z6_outfit"
        }
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "name": "Trousers",
    "detail": "Denim trousers",
    "category": "Unterteile",
    "brand": "QS by s.Oliver",
    "price": 49.99,
    "tags": { "new": "true", "sustainable": "true", "premium": "false" },
    "wishList": false,
    "shoppingCart": false,
    "colorVariants": [
      {
        "color": {
          "variant": "DarkBlue",
          "group": "Blue",
          "value": "#0d47a1"
        },
        "pictures": {
          "front": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2141250.59Z4_front",
          "flat": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2141250.59Z4_flat",
          "back": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2141250.59Z4_back",
          "outfit": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2141250.59Z4_outfit"
        }
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "name": "Trousers",
    "detail": "Trousers",
    "category": "Unterteile",
    "brand": "s.Oliver BLACK LABEL",
    "price": 79.99,
    "tags": { "new": "true", "sustainable": "false", "premium": "true" },
    "wishList": false,
    "shoppingCart": false,
    "colorVariants": [
      {
        "color": {
          "variant": "RosePink",
          "group": "Pink",
          "value": "#f8bbd0"
        },
        "pictures": {
          "front": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2142826.4757_front",
          "flat": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2142826.4757_flat",
          "back": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2142826.4757_back",
          "outfit": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2142826.4757_outfit"
        }
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "name": "Jeans Scube",
    "detail": "Jeans Scube / Relaxed Fit / High Rise / Straight Leg",
    "category": "Unterteile",
    "brand": "s.Oliver",
    "price": 79.99,
    "tags": { "new": "true", "sustainable": "false", "premium": "false" },
    "wishList": false,
    "shoppingCart": false,
    "colorVariants": [
      {
        "color": {
          "variant": "RustBlue",
          "group": "Blue",
          "value": "#1565c0"
        },
        "pictures": {
          "front": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2145746.53Z4_front",
          "flat": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2145746.53Z4_flat",
          "back": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2145746.53Z4_back",
          "outfit": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2145746.53Z4_outfit"
        }
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "name": "Hoodie",
    "detail": "Hoodie with fleece lining",
    "category": "Jacken & Mäntel",
    "brand": "QS by s.Oliver",
    "price": 79.99,
    "tags": { "new": "true", "sustainable": "false", "premium": "true" },
    "wishList": false,
    "shoppingCart": false,
    "colorVariants": [
      {
        "color": {
          "variant": "Black",
          "group": "Black",
          "value": "#000000"
        },
        "pictures": {
          "front": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2141622.9999_front",
          "flat": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2141622.9999_flat",
          "back": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2141622.9999_back",
          "outfit": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2141622.9999_outfit"
        }
      },
      {
        "color": {
          "variant": "NavyBlue",
          "group": "Blue",
          "value": "#1a237e"
        },
        "pictures": {
          "front": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2141622.5884_front",
          "flat": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2141622.5884_flat",
          "back": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2141622.5884_back",
          "outfit": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2141622.5884_outfit"
        }
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "name": "Hoodie",
    "detail": "Hoodie with fleece lining",
    "category": "Jacken & Mäntel",
    "brand": "QS by s.Oliver",
    "price": 79.99,
    "tags": { "new": "true", "sustainable": "false", "premium": "true" },
    "wishList": false,
    "shoppingCart": false,
    "colorVariants": [
      {
        "color": {
          "variant": "NavyBlue",
          "group": "Blue",
          "value": "#1a237e"
        },
        "pictures": {
          "front": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2141622.5884_front",
          "flat": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2141622.5884_flat",
          "back": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2141622.5884_back",
          "outfit": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2141622.5884_outfit"
        }
      },
      {
        "color": {
          "variant": "Black",
          "group": "Black",
          "value": "#000000"
        },
        "pictures": {
          "front": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2141622.9999_front",
          "flat": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2141622.9999_flat",
          "back": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2141622.9999_back",
          "outfit": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2141622.9999_outfit"
        }
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "name": "Indoor Jacket",
    "detail": "Indoor Jacket",
    "category": "Jacken & Mäntel",
    "brand": "s.Oliver BLACK LABEL",
    "price": 139.99,
    "tags": { "new": "true", "sustainable": "false", "premium": "true" },
    "wishList": false,
    "shoppingCart": false,
    "colorVariants": [
      {
        "color": {
          "variant": "DarkBlue",
          "group": "Blue",
          "value": "#1a237e"
        },
        "pictures": {
          "front": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2146198.5955_front",
          "flat": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2146198.5955_flat",
          "back": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2146198.5955_back",
          "outfit": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2146198.5955_outfit"
        }
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "name": "Outdoor Jacket",
    "detail": "Outdoor Jacket",
    "category": "Jacken & Mäntel",
    "brand": "s.Oliver",
    "price": 119.99,
    "tags": { "new": "true", "sustainable": "false", "premium": "false" },
    "wishList": false,
    "shoppingCart": false,
    "colorVariants": [
      {
        "color": {
          "variant": "LightBlue",
          "group": "Blue",
          "value": "#448aff"
        },
        "pictures": {
          "front": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2140533.5402_front",
          "flat": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2140533.5402_flat",
          "back": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2140533.5402_back",
          "outfit": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2140533.5402_outfit"
        }
      },
      {
        "color": {
          "variant": "NavyBlue",
          "group": "Blue",
          "value": "#1a237e"
        },
        "pictures": {
          "front": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2140533.5978_front",
          "flat": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2140533.5978_flat",
          "back": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2140533.5978_back",
          "outfit": "https://media.soliver.com/i/soliver/2140533.5978_outfit"
        }
      }
    ]
  }
]
}
